rbepartner.com 2014-03-12

# RBEPartner.com High profits and hourly plan. 2-level referral program.

Privacy Policy

## This Privacy Policy relates only to information stored through our website, and not to any information collected offline.

**Storing personal data**  
The personal information you are asked when registering for an account is: your name, contact e-mail and payment details. We also store some information we obtain from you when you interact with us. For example, we store your IP addresses, whenever you are using our website. This is done in order to enhance the security of your account and to prevent possible illegal access to your account. The collected information is used to communicate with you (send updates, news and account activity updates), create promotions and improve the site features. You are able to unsubscribe from receiving emails, at any time. We protect your privacy. Your information is accessed by only selected employees of RBE Partner. 

**Disclosure of data**  
All data given by any member to RBE Partner will be only privately used and not disclosed to any third parties. We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing or referring.

RBE Partner is not responsible or liable for any loss of data.

**Security**  
We have a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information. All supplied sensitive/financial information is transmitted via encrypted gateway provided by the payment systems. After a transaction, your private information will not be stored on our servers. The database of the site is highly encrypted and accessed by only those who have the special rights to do so.

**Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section governing the use of our website at  https://rbepartner.com/index.php?a=rules

**Your Acceptance**  
By using our site, you accept our Privacy Policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy:**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

Contact us if you have concerns about our Privacy Policy.
